

Profile

Experienced HR professional, I am working as an Assistant Manager in HR and Administration department where I am exposed to recruiting and staffing, induction and training, manpower planning and performance appraisal of the employees. I have introduced KPI and HRIS system in my organization that resulted in enhancing employee performance. I am keen to expand my experience in a more challenging position while also contributing towards the overall organizational development of the company.

Employment History

Assistant Manager, HR and Admin at BAC International Study Centre , Dhaka

July 2019 - Present

- Job posting, résumé scrutiny, short listing, arranging test & interviews
- Organizing on-boarding programme, induction and training programme for employees
- Maintaining and updating all personal files and database, updating and maintain HRIS
 - Promotion, Attendance, Leave & Holiday Management, making of salary report and others employee reports
 - Preparing appointment letter for selected candidates
 - Maintaining liaison with the external sources for having the qualified talent pool for the organization
 - Preparing KPI and Performance evaluation process
 - Preparation / Issue office note, office order & circular in respect of HR issues
 - -Issuing various type of letters/certificates to the employees and the students
 - Correspond with Edexcel local and UK office
 - Administrative reports, student reports and Edexcel report preparation.

Officer, HR and Admin at BAC International Study Centre, Dhaka February 2016 — June 2019

-

Internships

Intern at BASIC Bank LTD

March 2014 — June 2014

Worked in general banking department during the internship period

Research Publication

"Impact of Motivation Management on Employee Performance: A Study on Education Sector" Journal of Management, Dhaka University, Volume 13, No.1, January- June 2019, PP. 105-124.

June 2018 — June 2019

Details

House no# 28/C, Road no# 05, Dhaka, 1205, Bangladesh, +8801677261005

tasnem.tarannum222@gmail.com

Date of birth

23-09-1991

Nationality

Bangladeshi

Skills

Microsoft Office

IBM SPSS Statistics

Fast learning

Creativity and Innovation

Hard Working

Ability to Work in a Team

Languages

English

Bengali

Links

www.linkedin.com/in/tasnem-tarannum

Education

HRMC, Institute of Business Administration (IBA), Dhaka

April 2020 — May 2020

Management Development Program

Master of Business Administration (MBA), University of Dhaka

March 2015 — August 2018

Major: Human Resource Management

CGPA: 3.73

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), United International University

February 2009 — June 2014

Major: Human Resource Management & Accounting

CGPA: 3.51

HSC, Dhaka City College

February 2007 — June 2008

Business Studies

GPA: 5.00

SSC, Shaheed Ramiz Uddin Cantonment School

January 2005 — January 2006

Business Studies

GPA:4.69

Courses

Recruiting: Talent Acquisition and Hiring, Udemy

April 2020 — April 2020

Excel skills for Business: Essentials , Coursera (Macquarie University Sydney)

April 2020 — April 2020

Human Resources: Building a Performance Management System, Linkedin online learning

May 2020 — May 2020

Y Extra-curricular activities

HSBC case competition at United International University

May 2012 — June 2012

Cultural programs: Singing, Drama acts at Dhaka City College and United international University

Volunteered in job fairs at United International University

Club Coordinator at BAC International Study Centre

February 2016 — June 2019

Acted as club coordinator for BAC Cultural Clubs, BAC Photography Club, BAC Social Welfare Club, BAC IT Club and Sports Club.

◄ References

Dr. Sumon Das, Professor from Department of Management, University of Dhaka

sumondas@du.ac.bd · +8801711209239

Md. Sajjad Halim, Manager, HR and Admin from BAC International Study Centre

s.halim@bacbd.org · +8801715498683